<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Life | Meet @五角场民工]]></title>
  <link href="http://weiliv.github.io/blog/categories/life/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://weiliv.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-09-09T20:33:56+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://weiliv.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Wei Li]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Blog for Setting Goals]]></title>
    <link href="http://weiliv.github.io/blog/2013/04/20/my-first-blog-for-setting-goals/"/>
    <updated>2013-04-20T20:36:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://weiliv.github.io/blog/2013/04/20/my-first-blog-for-setting-goals</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I still remember when maintaining MSN space the first year I entered college. Then now I come back! Coz during the busy developping work, I rarely have time to write down some of the tips I need to achive. And what most of all, I should refect on my life regularly and regularly which is the exactly thing I seldom do.</p>

<p>As the title says, here some of goals are listed that I should cost my passion to acheive, at least try my best before 2014.1.1. Though today is Apr 20th, 2013, better later than never to set goals!</p>

<h3>Goals on Work</h3>

<p>Though I&rsquo;ve acted as an IOS developper for more than a half year, I&rsquo;m still a newbie definitly. And new techs come out year by year, learning should never stop.</p>

<ul>
<li>Learn more about ARC principle of the IOS, and try to migrate our project to ARC. ARC is a free of worry  achitecture that can save us a lot of time debugging and optimizing the memory issures which have anoyed us  since the last year when we start CYZS project. So we can &ldquo;release&rdquo; our dev resource on memory leaking or crashing, then focus on the logical optimization.</li>
<li>When a new ios project kicks off, automating UI test should join in.</li>
<li>Try to participate on the server devlepment, learn relative knowlege from Lucky and Tom.</li>
<li>Be active on building of the engineers' culture in our company, such as orgnizing some coding games and attending some tech conferences or forums as Karry pointed out.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Goals on Life</h3>

<ul>
<li>Keeping fit

<ul>
<li>Running, from now on maybe 150km? Recheck with Nike+.</li>
<li>Basketball, once for 2 weeks.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Guita, practice and practice.</li>
<li>Real estate, find one.</li>
<li>The most important one, you know that!</li>
</ul>


<p>Hope all the goals will be defeated at the end of 2013.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
